A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.28 (A2002) FA489
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2002.104: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2004; AC.2002.104; 11.79 Cubic Feet 9 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.104.1; 11.79 Cubic Feet 9 record storage boxes
    - RF 95040 #74 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE COAST (GHANA) - "SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY IN ACTION IN GHANA", 1992-1998 (Box R3515)
    - RF 93018 #12; RF 95043 #38 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL OF MUSEUMS (FRANCE) - WORKSHOP ON PROTECTION OF AFRICAN HERITAGE; TRAINING ON DOCUMENTATION STANDARDS, 1997-1999 (Box R3516)
    - RF 95043 #35 - RESEARCH AND TECHNOLOGY EXCHANGE GROUP (FRANCE) - NETWORK OF DONORS FOR AFRICAN MEDIA, 1996-1998 (Box R3516)
    - RF 95043 #36 - AFRICAN PUBLISHERS' NETWORK - MEETING ON THEIR VISION, PROGRAM AND STRATEGY, 1997 (Box R3516)
    - RF 95046 #10 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (AUSTRIA) - SAFETY OF GENETICALLY MODIFIED CROP PLANTS, 1997-1999 (Box R3516)
    - RF 95046 #12 - UNIVERSITY OF THE PHILIPPINES - INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS INTERNSHIP FOR LUZ B. OPENA, 1998 (Box R3516)
    - RF 95046 #14 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR GENETIC ENGINEERING AND BIOTECHNOLOGY (THAILAND) - MEETINGS TO EVALUATE RICE PROGRAM IN THAILAND; RELEASE OF TRANSGENIC RICE, 1998 (Box R3516)
    - RF 95047 #34 - FAMILY HEALTH INTERNATIONAL - UNSAFE ABORTION IN IVORY COAST AND GUINEA, 1995-1999 (Box R3516)
    - RF 95047 #41 - POPULATION COUNCIL, INC. - WOMEN'S HEALTH AND POPULATION POLICIES IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES, 1989-2000 (Box R3516, Box R3517)
    - RF 95047 #41 - POPULATION COUNCIL, INC. - WOMEN'S HEALTH AND POPULATION POLICIES IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1989-2000 (Box R3516, Box R3517)
    - RF 95047 #42 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - EFFECTIVENESS OF CRYOTHERAPY IN PREVENTING CERVICAL CANCER, 1994-2002 (Box R3517)
    - RF 95049 #110 - FOUNDATION FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT (INDONESIA) - LEAD NATIONAL PROGRAM IN INDONESIA, 1991-1998 (Box R3517)
    - RF 95050 #89 - MUNEER, SIDDIG EL TAYEB - GENDER DISPARITY IN BASIC EDUCATION IN NORTHERN KORDOFAN STATE, SUDAN, 1996-1998 (Box R3517)
    - RF 95050 #102 - KOUAME, AKA - FEMALE LABOR IN THE IVORY COAST, 1996-2002 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #103 - BASIRIKA, EDITH IRINE - SCHOOL ADMINISTRATION AND GIRLS' ACADEMIC PERFORMANCE AT SECONDARY-SCHOOL IN UGANDA, 1996-2002 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #106 - OSUNDE, AUGUSTINE UDINYIWE - FEMALE STUDENTS' ACADEMIC ACHIEVEMENT IN SCIENCE AT SECONDARY SCHOOL IN NIGERIA, 1996-1998 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #108 - BAGUMA, PETER KAKUBEIRE - FACTORS THAT INFLUENCE THE CHOICE OF SCIENCE SUBJECTS BY FEMALE STUDENTS AT SECONDARY-SCHOOL IN UGANDA, 1996-1999 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #109 - GBESSEMEHLAN, VICTOR - IMPACT ON GIRLS' ATTENDANCE IN PRIMARY SCHOOL OF EDUCATIONAL POLICY REFORMS IN BENIN, 1996-2002 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #110 - MATERI GIRLS' CENTRE (KENYA) - COMPUTER TRAINING COURSE, 1996-1998 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #111 - KOTOKOU, KODJO - LOW RATE OF GIRLS' SCHOOLING IN TOGO, 1996-2002 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #91 - HUSAIN, ABRAHAM - SOCIETAL PERSPECTIVES ON STATUS OF WOMEN AND ITS RELATIONSHIP TO EDUCATIONAL OPPORTUNITIES IN ETHIOPIA, 1996-2002 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #92 - GHANA - EDUCATION (MINISTRY OF) - CAUSES OF DROPOUT FROM BASIC EDUCATION, 1996-1998 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #94 - EZEH, DAVID NWOYE - INTERGRATED SCIENCE AMONG JUNIOR SECONDARY SCHOOL GIRLS IN NIGERIA, 1996-1998 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #95 - KYOMUGISHA, EUNICE LORNA - ACHIEVEMENT AND PERCEPTIONS IN ECONOMIC NUMERACY AMONG FEMALE UNIVERSITY STUDENTS IN UGANDA, 1996-2002 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #96 - KIGGUNDU, HERMAN - MEDIA IN INSTRUCTIONS AND PERFORMANCE IN DISTANCE EDUCATION AT SECONDARY LEVEL IN UGANDA, 1996-1999 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #97 - KASENTE, DEBORAH HOPE - SOCIO-ECONOMIC STATUS OF WOMEN IN UGANDA, 1996-1999 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95050 #98 - FORUM FOR AFRICAN WOMEN EDUCATIONALISTS (KENYA) - FEMSA'S SPECIAL FUND TO SUPPORT SMALL-SCALE INITIATIVES IN FEMALE EDUCATION, 1996 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95052 #97 - LINCOLN CENTER FOR THE PERFORMING ARTS - 1997 FESTIVAL, 1996-2000 (Box R3518)
    - RF 95054 #23 - ALASKA HUMANITIES FORUM - "COMMUNITIES OF MEMORY" PROJECT, 1995-1998 (Box R3519)
    - RF 95053 #1 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - "REBUILDING AMERICA'S SOCIAL CAPITAL" PROJECT, 1995-1999 (Box R3519)
    - RF 95054 #24 - BROADWAY AREA HOUSING COALITION - "NEIGHBORHOOD ARTS AND HISTORY PARTNERSHIP", 1996-2000 (Box R3519)
    - RF 95054 #25 - CENTER FOR THIRD WORLD ORGANIZING - "LEADERS IN COMMUNITY-BASED CULTURAL WORK" PROGRAM, 1996-1998 (Box R3519)
    - RF 95054 #28 - IDRIS ACKAMOOR AND CULTURAL ODYSSSEY - "MEDEA PROJECT: THEATER FOR INCARCERATED WOMEN", 1996-1999 (Box R3519)
    - RF 95054 #29 - SOUTHERNERS FOR ECONOMIC JUSTICE - YOUTH COORDINATING COMMITTEE, 1996-1997 (Box R3519)
    - RF 95054 #30 - WING LUKE ASIAN MUSEUM - "REMEMBERING OUR PAST/BUILDING OUR FUTURE", 1996-1999 (Box R3519)
    - RF 95054 #31 - ARIZONA COUNCIL ON THE HUMANITIES AND PUBLIC POLICY - "TRANSFORMING BARBED WIRE", 1997-1998 (Box R3520)
    - RF 95054 #32 - RHODE ISLAND BLACK HERITAGE SOCIETY - PERFORMING ARTS PROGRAM, 1996-2000 (Box R3520)
    - RF 95054 #34 - Youth for Social Change - Youth Coordinating Committee Project, 1996-1999 (Box R3520)
    - RF 95054 #36 - ESPERANZA PEACE AND JUSTICE CENTER - WORKSHOPS AND CULTURAL ARTS PROGRAMMING, 1997-1999 (Box R3520)
    - RF 95054 #39 - PEPATIAN - RACE ISSUES IN PUERTO RICAN COMMUNITIES IN SOUTH BRONX, 1997-2000 (Box R3520)
    - RF 95054 #73 - DEVELOPMENTAL STUDIES CENTER - READING AND LANGUAGE ARTS INSTRUCTION, 1995-1998 (Box R3520)
    - RF 96001 #397 - UNIVERSITY OF DELHI (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP: IMPROVED SUBMERGENCE TOLERANCE IN RICE, 1996-1999 (Box R3520)
    - RF 96001 #398 - PUNJAB AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - AGRONOMIC IMPROVEMENT OF BASMATI RICE, 1995-1999 (Box R3520)
    - RF 96001 #402 - MADURAI KAMARAJ UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - AGROBACTERI UM TUMEFACIENS AND INDICA RICE, 1994-2000 (Box R3520)
    - RF 96001 #406 - WASHINGTON STATE UNIVERSITY - RICE STARCH SYNTHESIS CONTROL, 1990-1998 (Box R3520)
    - RF 96001 #421 - PHILIPPINE RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - MOLECULAR METHODS AND HYBRID RICE PRODUCTION, 1995-1999 (Box R3521)
    - RF 96001 #423 - CAN THO UNIVERSITY (VIETNAM) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR NGUYEN VAN HUYNH AND LE THI KINH, 1994-1998 (Box R3521)
    - RF 96001 #431 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - MOLECULAR MARKERS AND RICE, 1996-1998 (Box R3521)
    - RF 96001 #443 - TATA INSTITUTE OF FUNDAMENTAL RESEARCH (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR VILLOO MORAWALA-PATELL, 1995-1999 (Box R3521)
    - RF 96001 #444 - BOSE INSTITUTE (INDIA) - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIP FOR A. N. LAHIRI MAJUMDER (RESCINDED), 1996-1998 (Box R3521)
    - RF 96001 #461 - INDIAN COUNCIL OF AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR P. ARTI, 1995-1998 (Box R3521)
    - RF 96001 #469 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - MOLECULAR MARKERS AND SUBMERGENCE TOLERANCE IN RICE, 1995-1999 (Box R3521)
    - RF 96001 #480; RF 89027 #15; RF 88003 #31 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF AGRICULTURAL SCIENCES - SEED INDUSTRY AND ITS CONSTRAINTS ON AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT, 1996-2002 (Box R3521)
    - RF 96001 #503 - CHINA NATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR HAN-WEI MEI, 1996-1999 (Box R3521)
    - RF 96001 #504 - TATA INSTITUTE OF FUNDAMENTAL RESEARCH (INDIA) - RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY TRAINING FOR GANGA RAO, 1996-1998 (Box R3521)
    - RF 96005 #87 - MALAWI AGROFORESTRY SYSTEMS, 1990-2001 (Box R3521)
    - RF 95007 #79; RF 96008 #80 - (FORUM ON AGRICULTURAL RESOURCE HUSBANDRY) - IN-COUNTRY WORKSHOPS, 1997-1999 (Box R3522)
    - RF 95022 #712; RF 96022 #713 - MUGIDDE, ROSE - ADIA: "ALGAL NITROGEN FIXATION IN LAKE VICTORIA", 1997-2001 (Box R3522)
    - RF 96005 #92 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (NETHERLANDS) - RESEARCH PRIORITIES SETTING, 1995-1999 (Box R3522)
    - RF 96007 #26 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE - 13TH SYMPOSIUM OF THE NEMATOLOGICAL SOCIETY OF SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1996-1997 (Box R3522)
    - RF 96008 #85 - INTERNATIONAL BIOMETRIC SOCIETY GROUP KENYA - FIFTH SCIENTIFIC MEETING OF INTERNATIONAL BIOMETRIC SOCIETY, 1997-1998 (Box R3522)
    - RF 96008 #88 - (FORUM ON AGRICULTURAL RESOURCE HUSBANDRY) - WORKSHOP FOR AGRONOMISTS, 1996-1999 (Box R3522)
    - RF 96011 #101 - TROPICAL DISEASES RESEARCH CENTER (ZAMBIA) - UNMET NEED FOR FAMILY PLANNING IN ZAMBIA, 1996-1999 (Box R3522)
    - RF 96011 #105 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR DIARRHOEAL DISEASE RESEARCH, BANGLADESH - SOUTH-SOUTH EXCHANGE, 1997-1999 (Box R3522)
    - RF 96011 #81 - CENTER FOR CULTURAL AND TECHNICAL INTERCHANGE BETWEEN EAST AND WEST - POPULATION DYNAMICS AND ECONOMIC GROWTH IN EAST ASIA, 1996-1999 (Box R3522)
    - RF 96015 #150 - FRIENDS OF THE MUSEUM OF THE BARRIO - EXHIBITION, "THE TAINO LEGACY", 1996-1998 (Box R3522)
    - RF 96015 #164 - FERRE FOUNDATION - (PUERTO RICO) - EXHIBITION "LOCUS GLOB@L", 1997 (Box R3522)
    - RF 96015 #165 - RUTGERS UNIVERSITY - EXHIBITION, "PAUL ROBESON: HERE I STAND", 1995-1998 (Box R3522)
    - RF 96020 #63 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES (CHINA) - WORKSHOP ON INDUSTRIAL COLLABORATION, 1995-1998 (Box R3522)
    - RF 96021 #6 - WORLD VISION - INTERNATIONAL POPULATION AND FAMILY PLANNING PROGRAMS EFFECT ON GIRLS, 1996-1998 (Box R3522)
    - RF 93050 #236; RF 96023 #241 - ANTORCHAS FOUNDATION (ARGENTINA) - INCUBATOR ACTIVITIES IN LATIN AMERICA, 1993-1999 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96022 #715 - GATHUA, JOEL MWANGI - ADIA: REDTAIL MONKEYS IN KAKAMEGA DISTRICT, 1997-2001 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96022 #725 - (AFRICAN DOCTORAL INTERSHIPS) - ELECTRONIC ACCESS TO AFRICAN THESES AND DISSERTATIONS, 1997-1999 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96022 #762 - ISSOUFOU KOLLO, ABDOURHAMANE - ADIA: ACREMONIUM WILT OF SORGHUM, 1998-2000 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96022 #783 - MUCHOKI, CHARLES H. K. - ACA: VEGETATION DYNAMICS AND LAND USE IN KENYA, 1996-1999 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #243 - RESOLUTION - "ENVISIONI NG COMMUNITY: NEW AFRICAN CINEMA 1997" PROJECT, 1996-1998 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #245 - AVILA DUENAS, IVAN - "VOCATION OF MARTYRDOM" FILM, 1997-1999 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #246 - LARA ESCOBEDO, GERARDO - "OUR AMERICAN FRIEND" DOCUMENTARY, 1997-2000 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #247 - RULFO, JUAN CARLOS - "LOS CAMINOS DE RULFO" DOCUMENTARY, 1996-2002 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #248 - BARRET, ELIZABETH - DOCUMENTARY, "STRANGER WITH A CAMERA", 1997-2004 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #250 - CHASNOFF, DEBRA - "RESPECT FOR ALL" VIDEOS, 1997-1999 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #252 - LEITMAN, RUTH - DOCUMENTARY, "ALMA", 1997-1998 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #253 - MENDIOLA, JIM - FILM, "AN AMERICAN ARTIST", 1997-2002 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #254 - NADERI, AMIR - FILM, "AVENUE A, B, C", 1995-1999 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #255 - NAKASAKO, SPENCER - FILM, "THE DONUT KINGS", 1997-2002 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #256 - NEGRON-MUNTANER, FRANCES - FILM, "THE SPLENDID LITTLE WAR", 1997-2002; 2004 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #257 - PITT, SUZAN - "LOS OTROS" FILM, 1997-2002 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #258 - PORTILLO, LOURDES - DOCUMENTARY "SELENA", 1997-2004 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #259 - VAZQUEZ, GUSTAVO - VIDEO, "TALES OF TIJUANA", 1997-1999 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #261 - YONEMOTO, BRUCE - MOVING IMAGE/MULTIMEDIA INSTALLATION, "EXTREMISM IN THE DEFENSE OF", 1997-1999 (Box R3523)
    - RF 96023 #262 - HARVESTWORKS - 1997 PROGRAM ACTIVITIES, 1997-1998 (Box R3523)
- AC.2002.108: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1978-2002; AC.2002.108; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.108.1; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RF 96024 #284 - PERFORMANCE SPACE 122 - PERFORMANCE PIECE, "LA SCARPETTA", 1996-1997 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96024 #292 - BRYANT PARK RESTORATION CORP. - "DANCING ON THE NET", 1996-1998 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96024 #299 - THICK DESCRIPTION - "CIVIL SEX", 1995-2000 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96024 #300 - ART SWEATS - "ARTS IN ACTION: THE NO ROLES BARRED PROJECT", 1997-1999 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96024 #302 - BLOOMSBURG THEATRE ENSEMBLE - DANCE-THEATER WORK "COAL PROJECT", 1997-1999 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96024 #303 - YERBA BUENA GARDENS CULTURAL CENTER - "THE SISTERS MATSUMOTO", 1997-1998 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96024 #304 - CITY LORE: THE NEW YORK CENTER FOR URBAN FOLK CULTURE - "RUMBOMBAZO", 1997-1999 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96024 #305 - CONTEMPORARY DANCE THEATRE - "AT THE CROSSROADS/NAGASAKI IN BLACK", 1997-1999 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96026 #14 - CORPORATION FOR SUPPORTIVE HOUSING - NEIGHBORHOOD EMPLOYMENT INITIATIVE, 1997-1998 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96026 #23 - CORPORATION FOR SUPPORTIVE HOUSING - COST-BENEFIT ANALYSIS AND NATIONAL POLICY SYMPOSIUM FOR NEXT STEP JOBS, 1997-1998 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96026 #25 - INDIANAPOLIS PRIVATE INDUSTRY COUNCIL - INDIANAPOLIS INDEPENDENCE INITIATIVE, 1996-1999 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96029 - COMMISSION ON TEACHER TRAINING AND DEVELOPMENT, 1995-1998 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96031 #2 - TASK FORCE FOR CHILD SURVIVAL AND DEVELOPMENT - CONFERENCE ON "GLOBAL DISEASE ELIMINATION AND ERADICATION AS PUBLIC HEALTH STRATEGIES", 1997-1998 (Box R3524)
    - RF 96031 #4 - UNITED NATIONS - INTERNATIONAL CHILDREN'S EMERGENCY FUND - TASK FORCE FOR CHILD SURVIVAL, 1984-1998 (Box R3525)
    - RF 96033 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH FELLOWSHIPS IN AGRICULTURE, 1983-1999 (Box R3526)
    - RF 96034 #110 - NETWORK OF AIDS RESEARCHERS OF EASTERN AND SOUTHERN AFRICA (KENYA) - WORKSHOP ON RESISTANCE TO AND MOTHER-TO-CHILD TRANSMISSION OF HIV, 1994-2000 (Box R3526)
    - RF 96034 #111 - INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL MEDICINE (BELGIUM) - DIFFERENTIAL SPREAD OF HIV IN AFRICA, 1995-1998 (Box R3526)
    - RF 96035 #502 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY RESOURCE AND TRAINING CENTER, 1978-2002 (Box R3526A, Box R3526)
    - RF 96035 #502 - UNIVERSITY OF PENNSYLVANIA - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY RESOURCE AND TRAINING CENTER - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1978-2002 (Box R3526A, Box R3526)
    - RF 96035 #508 - UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO - EVALUATIVE MANAGEMENT SKILLS, 1984-1998 (Box R3527)
    - RF 96035 #510 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - WORKSHOP ON BURDEN OF DISEASE, 1997-1998 (Box R3527)
    - RF 96035 #511 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - CLINICAL EPIDEMIOLOGY UNIT COMMUNICATION CAPACITY, 1996-1998 (Box R3527)
    - RF 96036 #57 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - WORKSHOP ON PROBLEM BASED LEARNING METHODOLOGY IN UGANDA, 1997-1998 (Box R3527)
    - RF 96039 #4 - NATIONAL HUMANITIES CENTER - ROLE OF RELIGION IN AMERICAN LIFE, 1996-2000 (Box R3527)
    - RF 96040 #42 - SOUTHERN AFRICAN BOOK FAIR TRUST - BOOK IN A DAY, 1993-1999 (Box R3527)
- AC.2002.112: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1990-2002; AC.2002.112; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2002.112.1; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    - RF 95049 #112; RF 96049 #113 - DEVELOPMENT AND ENVIRONMENT FOUNDATION (RUSSIA) - LEAD PROGRAM IN THE COMMONWEALTH OF INDEPENDENT STATES, 1990-1998 (Box R3528)
    - RF 96040 #43 - TUMBUKA DANCE CO. (ZIMBABWE) - PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT OF YOUNG DANCERS, 1996-1999 (Box R3528)
    - RF 96040 #44 - GREATER JOHANNESBURG METROPOLITAN COUNCIL (SOUTH AFRICA) - PARTICIPATION OF AFRICANS AT SECOND BIENALE, 1997-1999 (Box R3528)
    - RF 96040 #45 - FILM AND TV MARKET INITIATIVE (SOUTH AFRICA) - 1997 SOUTHERN AFRICAN INTERNATIONAL FILM AND TV MARKET; SEMINAR ON DEVELOPMENT OF FUTURE MARKETS, 1997-1998 (Box R3528)
    - RF 96040 #46 - COMMONWEALTH ASSOCIATION OF MUSEUMS (CANADA) - WORKSHOP ON CHILDREN IN AFRICAN MUSEUMS, 1997-1998 (Box R3528)
    - RF 96041 #43 - PALESTINIAN ACADEMIC SOCIETY FOR THE STUDY OF INTERNATIONAL AFFAIRS (ISRAEL) - 1997 ROUNDTABLE DISCUSSIONS ON PALESTINIAN CIVIL SOCIETY, 1997-1999 (Box R3528)
    - RF 96041 #45 - ASHTAR FOR THEATRE EDUCATION AND TRAINING (ISRAEL) - "ABU SHAKER'S AFFAIR", 1997 (Box R3528)
    - RF 96041 #46 - (UNDERSTANDING DIVERSITY IN MUSLIM SOCIETIES) - EXHIBITION, "MODERNITIES AND MEMORIES: RECENT WORKS FROM ISLAMIC WORLD", 1997-2000 (Box R3528)
    - RF 96048 #47 - INSTITUT DU SAHEL (MALI) - ADOLESCENT SEXUALITY AND FERTILITY IN MALI AND BURKINA FASO, 1997-2001 (Box R3528)
    - RF 96048 #51 - UNIVERSITY OF OUAGADOUGOU (BURKINA FASO) - SEXUALITY AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH AND FERTILITY OUTCOMES IN MALI AND BURKINA FASO, 1996-2000 (Box R3528)
    - RF 96049 #115 - DEVELOPMENT AND ENVIRONMENT LEADERSHIP FOR SOUTHERN AFRICA TRUST (ZIMBABWE) - LEAD PROGRAM, 1994-1998 (Box R3529)
    - RF 96049 #115 - DEVELOPMENT AND ENVIRONMENT LEADERSHIP FOR SOUTHERN AFRICA TRUST (ZIMBABWE) - LEAD PROGRAM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-1998 (Box R3529, Box R3530)
    - RF 96049 #116 - BRAZILIAN ASSOCIATION FOR LEADERSHIP DEVELOPMENT (BALD) - LDP NATIONAL PROGRAM IN BRAZIL, 1991-2002 (Box R3530)
    - RF 96049 #118 - CENTRE FOR RESEARCH ON ENVIRONMENT, ECOLOGY AND DEVELOPMENT (INDIA) - LEAD PROGRAM IN INDIA, 1994-1999 (Box R3530)
    - RF 96049 #120 - EL COLEGIO DE MEXICO - 21ST CENTURY LEADERSHIP DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM, 1991-2002 (Box R3530)
    - RF 96049 #121 - LEADERSHIP FOR ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT (PAKISTAN) - LEAD PROGRAM, 1995-1999 (Box R3531)
    - RF 96049 #121 - LEADERSHIP FOR ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT (PAKISTAN) - LEAD PROGRAM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1995-1999 (Box R3531)
    - RF 96049 #122 - FOUNDATION FOR ENVIRONMENTAL DEVELOPMENT AND EDUCATION IN NIGERIA (FEDEN) - LEAD NATIONAL PROGRAM IN NIGERIA, 1991-1998 (Box R3532)
    - RF 96049 #123 - INSTITUTE OF ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT (CHINA) - LEAD PROGRAM IN CHINA, 1993-1999 (Box R3532)
    - RF 96050 #1 - E CO. - BUSINESS CASE FOR A SOLAR DEVELOPMENT CORPORATION REGARDING SOLAR PHOTOVOLTAIC ENERGY, 1995-1999 (Box R3532)
    - RF 96051 #118 - YANOGO, FELIX O. - EMPLOYMENT FOR EDUCATED GIRLS IN OUAGADOUGOU, BURKINA FASO, 1997-2002 (Box R3532)
    - RF 96051 #124 - UNITED NATIONS CHILDREN'S FUND - "WORKSHOP ON INITIAL LESSONS LEARNED FROM IMPLEMENTING THE ALLIANCE FOR COMMUNITY ACTION ON FEMALE EDUCATION" IN GHANA, 1998-2002 (Box R3532)
    - RF 96056 #6 - AMERICANS FOR THE ARTS - INSTITUTE FOR COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT AND THE ARTS, 1997-1999 (Box R3532)